TANJA GODINIC

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER STUDENT

PROFILE

Extremely motivated to learn more about software development and grow my tech stack and skills. Currently studying for Full Stack Developer and hoping to get a junior developer role/internship.

My educational background is in business and marketing and my experience comes from over ten years in hospitality industry focused on event management.

EDUCATION

Code Institute

OCT 2020 - ONGOING

Diploma in Software Development

Learning the full stack - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python/Django

Faculty of Economics and Business

2001 - 2007

Masters Degree, Marketing

SKILLS

TECH

Learned so far Current

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- JQuery

Currently learning

- Python
- Django
- MongoDB
- Flask

SOFT

- Adaptable
- Quick to learn new things and technologies
- Good Listener
- Reliable
- Able to prioritize tasks
- Eye for details
- Responsible
- Fluent written and spoken English language

CONTACT

- +385 91 620 1381
- in www.linkedin.com/in/tanja-godinic
- https://github.com/TanYa-Go

HOBBIES

Movies | Travel | Excercise Healthy Cooking & Baking

EXPERIENCE

Events Manager

Cliff Hotel Group, Ireland

JAN 2017 - MAR 2019

Overall in charge of events department - organising and overseeing events for the Hotel

Conference & Events Sales Executive

O'Callaghan Hotels, Dublin, Ireland

DEC 2014 - DEC 2016

Organising events for four Dublin city center hotels

Reception & Reservations

Conference & Events Venue @ Mansionhouse

OCT 2012 - DEC 2014